Yes, I give warning; this is warning – a red card to the evil spirits right now.
Come out!
I say, "Out!"
You, evil spirit - leave my people!
Leave my people!
She is possessed with spirit of flirting and this spirit has been in the family.
It will be cast out.
She is like a dog.
Dog means, she is just flirting with any man.
Anytime the spirit comes upon her, she is just like a prostitute.
She is not going to a hotel but she is flirting around.
That is the problem she has.
Jesus loves her.
What you said is true.
I came here for freedom.
I have been praying to God so many times to set me free.
After the service, the woman who had received the prophecy met T.B. Joshua for her deliverance.
Here, the man of God ministers prayer and deliverance, with a touch, in the name of Jesus Christ,
backed up, accompanied by all the power of heaven.
Her deliverance takes place and she is free.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Roberta and I'm coming from Spain.
First of all, I would like, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ, to tell everything, to expose the devil
and say my testimony today.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Indeed, this testimony is to put shame to the devil for what he has done
and to glorify Jesus for His deliverance in your life.
Share with us what was the word of prophecy you received last week Sunday.
T.B. Joshua prophesied that I had the spirit of flirting and it comes from my family
and the spirit was putting me into the prostitution, but Jesus loves me and He took me out - He saved me.
Thank You, Jesus.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Share with us your experience in life; how can you confirm this prophecy to be true?
My family was a disaster.
Everyone...
I didn't even experience what it means to have a family because everyone is divorced;
my aunts, my mother and father...
It was a disaster - I was suffering so much.
I was praying, "Lord..."
I remember - when I was little, I wasn't a Christian and I just said, "Me - I am not gonna live like that".
I was praying, "God, rescue me".
When I was about 18 years old, my mother used to say, "Oh, women in our family are very sexual. Don't worry -
it's fine. Go and flirt with the men. It's nothing bad"
I always had this temptation to talk to guys and get the things I wanted.
I never understood why...
Since I was very young, men used to look at me incredibly.
I never understood what was wrong with me.
Even when I was dressing up simply, without make-up, without anything, I used to get so much attention
that I couldn't handle it.
I didn't have a Spirit of God, at that time.
I remember, when I was about 18 years old, when I was going back home from the gym,
there was a man following me and when I entered my house
he grabbed me and touched my intimate parts.
He wanted to pull me out of the house.
But he didn't know that I lived in that neighbourhood and my mother opened the door, and she saw him -
then he dropped me on the floor and ran away.
So, God was saving me always from all kinds of situations.
While I was in serious relationships, I didn't understand why I was looking at the men,
why I had this feeling for the men, why I wanted...
I couldn't understand.
My heart didn't want that but my body, my flesh...
I was even scared to look at the guy, because when I looked at him, he was getting crazy.
When I go to the gym, I don't even want to look at anyone because I feel like men wait for my eye-contact.
Once I accepted Jesus Christ a year ago, the spiritual fight started because I started to feel so bad about it.
I knew I wasn't having sex with them but I felt so much guilt and disgust inside of me.
I was asking the Lord, "What's happening? Why do I feel this spiritual fight inside of me?"
What was in my head... and it's true...
In my mind I knew that If I wasn't a Christian, I would be going around with all the men and would have pleasure,
I wouldn't be able to finish that.
That was in my head.
That really scarred me.
I remember one time I came back home because I couldn't be in the church...
I thought, "I am a Christian, but I feel so dirty and bad".
I came back home and I was praying to the Lord - I said, "Take my life back to heaven and finish with me,
or deliver me, because I don't want to live like that."
So, we can really understand that this spirit of flirting, of a dog,
has really pushed you around and made your life miserable.
You mentioned earlier that when you went to a gym it was almost
as if men were waiting to have contact with your eyes.
What can you say?
Do you think there was a power in your eyes?
Yes.
I will tell you one thing - it is for girls, listen to me.
I was a Christian already and I loved God - this is why I am here delivered now.
A month ago, when I went to the gym, the nice guys were saying to me, "You are so good, so nice".
You might think maybe he could be a Christian in the future, your husband or whatever.
I used to say, "I am a Christian. I can't meet with you."
When they start to talk with you and have more confidence, they would say,
"Oh, I would like to read the Bible with you. I would like to know about God. Maybe you could lead me to God?"
It is a lie!!
Even before my coming to The SCOAN, there was a man who...
Thanks God that I didn't sleep with him.
You know what he told me when I was going home?
He said, "From now on, you are going to think about me, and you will beg me to call you back,
and to have sex with me, and to finish what we started."
That is demon.
That is not a guy who wants to know the Bible, that's not a Christian and it is not from God!
Wow, we can really understand how these spirits...
Let's put our hands together for Jesus
for rescuing our sister from what could have been a very terrible life indeed.
Tell us, what were some of the things, that this spirit of flirting has pushed you to do,
that now, being delivered you find yourself regretting.
You know, I regret...
How to say?
This spirit...
If I had died, I would have gone to hell.
That is what I regret most - that I...
I mean...
That was the thing: God saved my soul, He saved my spirit because if I had died, I would have gone to hell
God is holy and He hates sin.
That is what I regret: doing sin, not being delivered and not fighting with devil harder -
but it is difficult when you are not delivered.
OK. We understand.
Now, for the glory of God - you said you wanted to put devil to shame
for what he has used you to do in the past;
tell us some of those worst experiences you had with this spirit of flirting and dog.
What are the things you want to confess now, in the presence of God?
Guilt, disgust...
I had dreams of having sex with men.
I also had a dream where the man was saying to me, "You are not gonna achieve it. You are nothing.
You are disgusting. I will take you. You will not achieve what you want to."
They used to talk to me through the people, even Christians.
Can you imagine that they told me, "You gonna stay always like that. You will not change."?
That's how devil was manipulating me.
That was the worst experience to me.
Also, I thought that I would never get married because I could not settle.
I was with a person and I was thinking about doing something with other men.
I didn't want that but I couldn't deal with it.
It was just in my mind; it was making me crazy.
I had a depression.
I remember - for seven months I used to wake up, go to the bathroom and cry...
I couldn't even work.
So, you mean that even when you were in a serious relationship with someone,
this spirit of flirting would not stop.
It would still be pushing you to look for other people, even...
Yes. And I remember...
For example I was in a serious relationship and I used to blame my ex-boyfriend and say,
"Don't you want to look at other girls and to do something with them? Because I do."
I was blaming him.
I was asking him, "Don't you feel like that? Don't lie. I feel that way."
I couldn't understand.
I was feeling that everyone had this kind of feeling.
When I talked to my mother and said, "I don't know what's happening to me. I feel like going with men to flirt,
and that was like 'feeding' me, giving me strength.”
I didn't understand that.
I even asked Christians what was wrong with me, because I could say "No".
I wanted to go for a dinner, to get attention - it seemed like it gave me power, confidence, strange feeling to me.
At the same time, it made you feel like you had power and confidence.
How did they make you feel about yourself, knowing that you kept having eyes for every man in the room?
When I wasn't a Christian, that made me to feel cool.
When I became a Christian, without my conscience, I started to feel guilty and very bad.
That's how the spiritual battle started.
When I started to read the Word of God, when Jesus touched my heart, I felt so bad.
I even thought that God didn't love me.
Right now, after the deliverance, every time when...
Because we are human...
If I had a mind, the thought or something...
When Prophet T.B. Joshua said, "Jesus loves her", this mind was like a fire to every thought coming to my head.
It is an incredible feeling.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
You received your deliverance, as we saw on the screen.
Tell us what was your experience, when the man of God prayed for you.
It's incredible.
I was praying for deliverance a long time ago.
I went to my church and pastor prayed for me to cast out the demon.
I didn't know what kind of demon I had, but I knew I had one.
That's very important to ask God, to reveal if you are delivered or not.
I knew I was not delivered.
When other pastors prayed for me I didn't feel anything, and it was like "really?"
but when T.B. Joshua was praying with the power of God, my body...
I couldn't handle my body anymore.
I was loosing the conscience.
At the same time, my spirit started to feel happy.
I started to pray with T.B. Joshua saying, "Go out, in the name of Jesus".
Then the demon manifested.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Now, you have been with us, in the church for another week, since your deliverance.
Tell us what are the changes you have seen now.
You know, I could...
The most important change for me - that's something I would like to maintain, for that I pray to God everyday...
When I read the Bible it enters my heart.
Before I used to read the Bible and it was like, "I want to understand but I don't. It doesn't touch me anyhow."
Right now, I read it and I remember it.
Can you believe that?
Hallelujah! Puts your hand together for Jesus!
What can you say about this spirit of flirting, that you have been delivered from?
Are you still having the urge, are you still looking around, anytime you move around?
I can look but I don't feel anything.
I mean, I'm not gonna be like this, you know.
I look at the person but I don't have any feeling, like talking or whatever.
That's a good feeling - yeah!
Hallelujah! Let's put your hands together for Jesus!
What a wonderful deliverance.
Now, that you are free, we want you to tell your word of advice to people watching and listening to you
all over the world.
I was praying, "Lord, what could I say to people?"
That is what came to my head.
I will read from 1 John 1:6.
"If we say that we have fellowship with Him, and walk in darkness, we lie and do not practice the truth.
But if we walk in the light as He is in the light, we have fellowship with one another,
and the blood of Jesus Christ His Son cleanses us from all sin." 1 John 1:6-7
So, my message would be, "Check your life. Are you walking in the light? Are you a liar?"
Because I was a liar.
At some moment I said to God, "God, if I die today, I will go to hell. Help me. Save me."
Now, I'm here - wooo!
Thank You, Jesus!
Amen!
To God be the glory!
Lastly, we want you to give a word of advice to women or even men watching you,
who maybe find themselves having the similar problem of this flirtatious spirit.
What should they do?
Well, that worked for me.
First of all, ask God to reveal... to deliver you.
Because without deliverance, with the mind or body it's impossible.
Our flesh cannot defeat satan - it's impossible.
We need the Holy Spirit.
First of all, we need to ask God for a deliverance and for the strength to say "No".
We need to please God, not people!
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We encourage you sister; you are delivered by the Word of God - make God's Word the standard for your life
to maintain this deliverance, and the best is yet to come for you, in Jesus' name.
Thank you, in Jesus name.